Guide to the B.F. Stanton papers, 1950-2010
Stanton, B.F. papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
B.F. Stanton papers, 1950-2010
21-43-3851
B. F.(Bernard Freeland), Stanton 1925-
3 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Publications, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, publications and subject files concerning his work in the Dept. of Agricultural Economics and as president of the American Agricultural Economics Association and vice president of the International Association of Agricultural Economists.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor emeritus in the Dept. of Applied Economics and Management and a member of the Cornell class of 1949.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, publications and subject files concerning his work in the Dept. of Agricultural Economics and as president of the American Agricultural Economics Association and vice president of the International Association of Agricultural Economists.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Stanton, B. F.1925-; American Agricultural Economics Association; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.Class of 1949.; International Association of Agricultural Economists.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Applied Economics and Management; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Agricultural Economics.
Subjects:
Agriculture--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/3851
See also the publication Farm Journal and Cornell Gentleman.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. Subject Files
Series III. Publications
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence, A-Z, 1968-2007 (Box 1)
- Subject Files
  - Columbia University Project, 1992-1997 (Box 1)
  - IAAE - Dartington Summary and Cornell Meeting, 2005 (Box 1)
  - MONY Project, 1990 (Box 1)
  - NITRA Project - Slovakia, 1993-1996 (Box 1)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1987 (Box 1)
  - MONY Project, 1994 (Box 1)
  - JH- Farmland Investor, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Farm Credit Banks of Springfield- "Outside" Board Member, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Memberships, Honors, Citations, Degrees, etc., 1951-1998 (Box 1)
  - International Association of Agricultural Economists (IAAE) - Board of Directors of the Fund for IAAE, 1970-1979 (Box 2)
  - Fund for the IAAE, 1980-1991 (Box 2)
  - Fund for ICAE- Japan Branch - Kanai, Kobayashi - IAAE, 1994; 1997 (Box 2)
  - University of Helsinki, 2001-2003 (Box 2)
  - Fund for ICAE - J. von Braun - IAAE, 1995-1997 (Box 2)
  - Fund for ICAE - Dr. R.J. Hildreth - IAAE, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - History of the IAAE, 1973-2000 (Box 2)
  - IAAE Meetings, 1985; 1988 (Box 2)
  - IAAE Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
  - IAAE - Dr. Saburo Yamada and Japanese Organizing Committee Members, 1991 (Box 2)
  - IAAE - Travel Grants, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Fund for ICAE, 1995-1997 (Box 2)
  - Walt Armbruster - IAAE, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Cowbell Bulletin and Program, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Cowbell Bulletin, 1991; 1994 (Box 2)
  - Stanton China Visit, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Lee Teng-Hui Visit, 1995 (Box 2)
  - The Book Project - Agricultural Economics at Cornell, A History, 2001-2002 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence with Ruth Gerlach on Warren Book, 2003 (Box 2)
  - G. F. Warren - Materials for Book, November 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Warren Farm and Family, November 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - G. F. Warren - Key Talks for Quotes for 1920s and 1930s, November 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - G. F. Warren - Ithaca Journal Story, February 16, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Warren Book, 2007-2008 (Box 2)
  - Warren Book - Time Article, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Beth Fontana, November 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Roger Haydon - C. U. Press, November 13, 2008 (Box 2)
  - Choices Article on G. F. Warren, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Quota Programs: Potential Problems, 2000-2009 (Box 2)
  - Agricultural Economics - Grolier, Inc., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Drafts of Chapter in the Columbia History of the 20th Century, 1992 (Box 2)
  - People, Land and Farms - N.Y.- Warren, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - The Northeast Agricultural Leadership Assembly, 1979 (Box 2)
  - Sabbatic Leave, USDA, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Stanton, B. F. - Sabbatic Leaves, Biographical Data Sheets, Transcripts, Birth Certificates, 1958-1976 (Box 2)
  - The Australian National University - Miscellaneous Material, Spring 1976 (Box 2)
- Publications
  - List of Publications for B. F. Stanton (Box 3)
  - Publications, Chronological by Year, 1950-1999 (Box 3)